[MUSIC]
My God, mom, why didn't you knock?
>> Don't be ashamed, I've
seen your little cock before.
Besides, I'm your step mom and you're
18, so you can do whatever you want.
>> I know, but still, what the hell?
>> Well, well, Corey is waiting
for you in the dining room.
>> Who?
>> I can't believe you,
Corey took weeks of her work so
she can tutor you and you're
not failing your finals.
And you're just laying there jerking off.
>> Corey who?
>> You are so fucking ungrateful.
Corey is my best friend from
college, valedictorian of our class.
>> Mom, please, no, it's my day off.
Mom, please, no, I don't wanna study.
>> Well, you should talk
about this before failing.
>> I don't wanna study on my day off.
>> Come on, get up.
>> Let me just finish here.
>> Rico, I don't want to know
what you're doing in your free time.
I will tell you what,
if you go right now and be
nice to my friend, I will
be nice to you at night.
>> What does that even mean?
>> It's a prize you're
going to see, so get your ass
off your bed, come down and
pay attention to your tutor.
>> Fine.
Sorry I was late.
>> I get it.
You're probably really tired
from studying for all these exams.
>> Yeah, and I still have to study
on weekends and I'm still struggling.
>> I get it.
Trust me, once we're
done with all the tutoring,
it'll click in your head and
it'll become so much easier.
So I got your first problem for you.
Go ahead, start solving that one.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[SOUND]
>> It's not coming to your head?
>> No.
>> Let's try something a
little different, shall we?
Let's try.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Something a little simpler this time.
>> Perfect, let's see.
>> Think of the thought process, go
down the line and you're solving for x.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[BLANK_AUDIO] Is this right?
Okay, let's take a look.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Very, very close, let's try something else.
Let's try to kind of
reverse it, we'll do this.
[BLANK_AUDIO] Okay.
>> Okay.
>> Perfect.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Just keeping working,
one by one, step at a time.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[BLANK_AUDIO] How's this?
But then you missed, you see how you
missed the x, you didn't bring it over?
Right here?
>> Yeah.
>> That's where you messed up on that one.
So we'll just scratch that part out.
There, Nico, what are you doing?
Were you staring at my tits?
>> I'm so sorry, please don't tell my mom.
>> What do you think you were doing?
>> Well, I promise not to
tell my mom, please, it's just.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> It's fine, Rico, it's fine.
It's perfectly normal for
a young man like yourself.
And like honestly, what
do you think you were doing?
>> Well, and I think I had
a little trouble in my last
class because I kind of
had a crush on my teacher.
I just have a thing for
teachers and seeing you,
you're so hot and I just,
I couldn't help myself.
I'm really sorry, please don't tell my mom.
>> Like I said, it's perfectly
normal for a young man like yourself.
And thank you for thinking me to be so hot.
Having a confident, mature woman sitting
next to you, I can see how that can happen.
And you know what, Rico, I'm not
as prudish as your other teachers.
Why don't we get your mind off of
maybe my tits and we'll get back to study.
>> Okay.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> What do you think?
>> I think they're amazing.
>> Mm-hm.
>> My God.
They're so perfect and round.
>> Uh-huh.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> You have such great tits.
>> Thank you.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> Okay, now that we've got your mind
off of my titties, you've seen them.
Why don't you go ahead
and solve that problem?
That's it.
And if you study very hard and pass your
next test, I'll give you a little treat.
>> Okay, let's keep studying.
[BLANK_AUDIO] >> How's this?
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> Much better, Rico.
Much, much better.
>> Perfect.
>> Great job.
>> Thank you.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> Here, say another one.
>> Mom, I thought I told you a lot.
>> Cory told me you are very nice with her.
You listen, I'm happy.
>> Yeah?
>> And I wanna give you
a little present for that.
>> But you're my mom.
>> No, Sile, I'm your stepmom.
And besides, I know
you have a crush on Cory.
So you just relax, enjoy,
you can think about her.
[BLANK_AUDIO] >> Oh, yeah.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> Feels good, right?
>> Yeah, feels great.
Now you can think about Cory, Tits.
>> Yeah.
>> She's hot, right?
>> Very.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, fuck.
[BLANK_AUDIO] >> Oh, shit.
[BLANK_AUDIO] >> Mm-hm.
[BLANK_AUDIO] >> Yeah.
[BLANK_AUDIO] >> Fuck.
[BLANK_AUDIO] >> Oh, fuck.
>> Yeah.
>> Just like this.
>> Yeah, yeah.
[BLANK_AUDIO] >> Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
>> Mm-hm.
>> Oh, fuck.
Oh, gotta go.
>> Yeah?
>> Oh, fuck.
>> Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
>> Now you feel better.
>> Yeah.
>> I am glad.
That was amazing.
>> Mm-hm.
>> Shit.
>> Oh, fuck.
>> You are going to relieve
your tension in my mouth.
>> Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That was so bad.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Just keep on that.
Oh, fuck.
>> Oh, fuck.